buncee.com 2016-12-07

# Buncee | Terms and Privacy

Terms of Service for Buncee LLC ~  
Statement of Rights and Responsibilities 

This Agreement sets forth the Terms of Service which apply to any individual accessing [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), <https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools>***, and/or our mobile applications Buncee Bits, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool, all hereinafter referred to as “Buncee”. The Statement of Rights and Responsibilities derived from Buncee principles governs Buncee’s relationship with Users who interact with Buncee. By using or accessing Buncee, you agree to this statement, the User Agreement and Privacy Policy. If you are using Buncee on behalf of a company, school or district, or other legal entity, you, the company, the school or district, and/or other legal entity, are bound by this agreement. If you do not want to become a User, do not accept the Agreement, do not access, view, download or otherwise use any Buncee webpage, mobile application, information or services. By becoming a User, you acknowledge that you have read and understood the terms and conditions of this Agreement and that you agree to be bound by all of its provisions. If you disagree with any of the terms and conditions stated, please stop using [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), <https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools>, and any of Buncee’s mobile applications. *** <https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools> is our Buncee for Schools and Districts product. Each district is supplied with it’s own private domain, i.e. yourdistrict.edu.buncee.com and an administrative dashboard, i.e. yourdistrict.admin.edu.buncee.com. 

Sharing and Communicating Content and Information

While Buncee owns all the artwork (backgrounds, stickers, messages etc) provided in the tool’s built in library, you own all of the content and information that you post on Buncee, and you control how it is shared and used through settings. You may request its deletion at any time from [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), or <https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools>; however, if the information or content has already been shared with others and they have not deleted it, or it was copied based on your "Copyable" settings or stored by other Users, Buncee cannot guarantee its deletion. Additionally, you grant Buncee a nonexclusive, irrevocable, worldwide, perpetual, unlimited, assignable license, fully paid up and royalty-free right to us to copy, prepare derivative works of, improve, distribute, publish, remove, retain, add, process, analyze, use and commercialize, in any way now known or in the future discovered, any information you provide, directly or indirectly to Buncee, including but not limited to any user generated content, ideas, concepts, techniques or data to the services, you submit to Buncee, without any further consent, notice and/or compensation to you or to any third parties. 

Downloading Intellectual Property

[https://www.buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [https://www.edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), <https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools>, and Buncee’s mobile applications, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, Buncee Bits, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool, contain copyrighted material, trademarks and other proprietary information, including, but not limited to, text, photos, video, graphics, music, and sound, portions of which are owned by Buncee LLC. The contents created by Buncee, in their entirety, of [https://www.buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [https://www.edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), <https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools>, and Buncee’s mobile applications, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, Buncee Bits, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool, are copyrighted as a collective work/compilation. No Visitor may modify, publish, transmit, or participate in the transfer or sale, create derivative works, or in any way exploit, any of the content, in whole or in part. Except as otherwise expressly permitted under copyright law, no copying, redistribution, retransmission, publication or commercial exploitation of downloaded material will be permitted without the express written permission of Buncee, LLC. 

Uploading Intellectual Property

No user shall upload, post or otherwise make available on [https://www.buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [https://www.edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), <https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools>, and Buncee’s mobile applications, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, Buncee Bits, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool, any material protected by copyright, trademark, or other proprietary right, without the express written permission of the owner of the copyright, trademark, or other proprietary right. The burden of determining that any material is not protected by copyright lies with the user, who shall be solely liable for any damage resulting from any infringement of copyright, proprietary right, or any other harm resulting from such a submission. By submitting Buncees created to any public area of [https://www.buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [https://www.edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), <https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools>, and Buncee’s mobile applications, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, Buncee Bits, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool, a user grants or warrants that the owner of any such material has expressly granted Buncee, LLC the royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, non-exclusive right and license to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate and distribute such material, in whole or in part, worldwide and/or to incorporate it in other works in any form, media or technology now known or hereafter developed for the full term of any copyright that may exist in such material. User also grants Buncee LLC the right to edit, copy, publish and distribute any material made available by user on [https://www.buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [https://www.edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), <https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools>, and Buncee’s mobile applications, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, Buncee Bits, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool.. (please see ‘User Options’ below to learn more about each Buncee product) When utilizing Buncee’s Universal Search or Web Image Search features on [https://www.buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [https://www.edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), <https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools>, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool, Web Image Search is powered by Pixabay, while 360 Image Search is powered by Flickr. Images from Pixabay and Flickr are released under Creative Commons CC0. To the extent possible under law, uploaders of Pixabay and Flickr have waived their copyright and related or neighboring rights to these Images. You can view Pixabay’s Terms of Service [here](https://pixabay.com/en/service/terms/). You can view Flickr’s Terms of Service [here](https://policies.yahoo.com/us/en/yahoo/terms/utos/index.htm). 

Payment Terms

Personal Information:

When you purchase an account, we have security measures in place and take reasonable precautions to protect against the loss, misuse and unauthorized access of personal information under our control. 

Safe Purchase Policy:

The security of your personal information is a high priority, and we have taken numerous steps to ensure that it is processed confidentially, accurately and securely. The [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), and <https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools> websites use encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), to protect your personal information during data transport. SSL encrypts ordering information such as your name, address and credit card number. In addition, [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), and <https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools> serves all of its traffic over HTTPS. With HTTPS in place, all interactions with Buncee are undecipherable by an outside observer. HTTPS is the same system that many sensitive websites, such as banks, use to secure their traffic. All ordering information and payment processing is collected by PayPal for [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/) accounts, and Stripe for [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/) accounts. Buncee LLC does not collect, use, store, or share credit card or bank account information. Although these safeguards are in place and monitored regularly, Buncee LLC cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us by e-mail, and you do so at your own risk. Please refer to PayPal’s Privacy Policy [here](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/useragreement-full), PayPal’s User Agreement [here](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/useragreement-full), PayPal's Legal Agreements [here](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/legalhub-full), and Stripe’s Privacy Policy [here](https://stripe.com/us/privacy), and Stripe’s Terms of Service [here](https://stripe.com/us/terms). 

Payment:

You agree to pay the then-current fee for the account type you have selected. The current fee for the account type you have selected will automatically and immediately be posted to your credit card if that is your chosen method of payment, or charged by PayPal for [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/) accounts, or Stripe for [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/) accounts to your payment instrument or account. All purchases requests on <https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools> can be made via purchase order., and payment can be made by check, or credit card/PayPal payment through PayPal. Fees charged for one account type may not be credited towards other account types. All currency references are in U.S. dollars. 

Recurring Billing:

Buncee LLC offers three methods of subscription payment: PayPal for [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/) accounts through here or Stripe for [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/) accounts through here, credit card payment, and payment by purchase order / by check (for some of our products only). If you are requesting to pay by check, contact us at [info@buncee.com](mailto:info@buncee.com). Your subscription will be activated after payment has been received. Recurring payments established through PayPal or Stripe can be cancelled through your account with PayPal or Stripe, or through [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/) for bunceePLUS users, or [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/) for bunceeEDU PLUS users. 

Month-to-Month:

Payment: Every month we will bill your Paypal Account or Credit Card on [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), and your Stripe Account or Credit Card on [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/) the stated monthly fee. Once you have successfully completed the sign-up process and your payment is confirmed, your membership will begin. Your next recurring payment will automatically be deducted monthly after your initial payment. Renewal: Thereafter, we will renew your monthly subscription every month automatically for accounts created on [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), unless you cancel, and we will renew your monthly subscription every month for 12 months for accounts created on [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), unless you cancel. Accounts created on [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/) will require the user to renew the subscription after 12 months. The price is subject to change, but we will always let you know before the price changes. 

Annual:

Payment: At sign-up, your Paypal Account or Credit Card will be billed the stated annual fee on [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/) accounts, and your Stripe Account or Credit Card will be billed the stated annual fee on [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/) accounts. Once you have successfully completed the sign-up process and your payment is confirmed, your membership will begin. Your next recurring payment will automatically be deducted 12 months after your initial payment for [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/) accounts, unless you cancel. Accounts created on [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/) will require the user to renew the subscription every year. Renewal: The annual subscription price paid is valid for 12 months. Thereafter, we will renew your contract every 365 days automatically for [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/) accounts, unless you cancel. Accounts created on [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/) will require the user to renew the subscription every 12 months. The price is subject to change, but we will always let you know before the price changes. 

Cancellation of Subscription:

Payment for monthly and annual subscriptions is non-refundable. If you cancel your account, your cancellation will take effect immediately, but you will be able to use Buncee until the end of your paid subscription term. At the end of your paid subscription, if your account was a bunceePLUS account, your account will revert to a bunceeFREE account and will be subject to the restrictions of a bunceeFREE account. If your account was a bunceeEDU PLUS account or a bunceeEDU Schools account, your account will NOT revert to a bunceeEDU FREE account, and you will no longer be able to access your own Buncees, your Sub-Accounts, or their Buncee creations - until the time that you decide to renew your paid bunceeEDU PLUS subscription or bunceeEDU Schools subscription. To cancel your bunceeEDU Schools subscription, the school or district administrator can click ‘delete application’ from their [Clever](https://schools.clever.com/signup/buncee) dashboard. Once the edu.buncee application is deleted, all administrators, teachers, and students will be unable to access their Buncee accounts and/or Buncee creations.. To cancel a subscription that uses Google Classroom to sync student data with Buncee, the school or district administrator can contact Buncee at [info@buncee.com](mailto:info@buncee.com). Buncee, LLC has no obligation to make your content available to you after cancellation. However, at any point during your subscription, you can backup your data on your computer using our Download as a .jpg or PDF features where provided. If you cancel your account before the end of the term for which you paid, you will not be given any refund. 

Deactivation of Paid Account:

Payment for monthly and annual subscriptions is non-refundable. If you deactivate your account, your deactivation will be effective immediately, regardless of subscription term. You will not be given any refund even if you deactivate your account before the end of the term for which you paid. In deactivating your account, you also deactivate your selected payment and will not be charged for the next subscription term. If you have deactivated your account in error, or wish to reactivate your account, simply login, and click the “Reactivate” button on the Reactivate Account Page. If you reactivate your account before the end of your paid subscription term, you will not be charged for the remainder of that term. 

Termination:

If your payment is invalid for any reason your paid bunceePLUS account will revert to a bunceeFREE account and will be subject to the limitations of a bunceeFREE account. Your paid bunceeEDU PLUS account or your paid bunceeEDU Schools account will NOT revert to bunceeEDU FREE account and will be put on hold until the payment has cleared; however, in any such cases Buncee reserves the right to cancel your account entirely. Buncee, LLC further reserves the right to cancel, or revert to a bunceeFREE account status, the account of any user who attempts to fraudulently obtain bunceeEDU pricing. 

User Options

Buncee offers a number of ways to publicly or privately share your creations with others. You can choose to subscribe as a bunceeFREE or bunceePLUS user on [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), or a bunceeEDU FREE or bunceeEDU PLUS user on [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), or our mobile application, Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool. Schools and districts can subscribe to bunceeEDU Schools (powered by Google Classroom or Clever) on <https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools>. 

buncee.com Accounts

bunceeFREE Users:

After creating a Buncee, you have the option to make your creation public or private. A public Buncee will be posted on the Latest Creations page and the corresponding Category page, and all of the content you create including all of the information within your Buncees will be available to anyone who has access to the internet. You have the option to email a public Buncee, post it to your favorite social media networks, share its public URL through any means, or embed it on other websites or blogs. Public Buncees can be viewed by other Buncee users, will appear in the searchable Buncee database, and will be available for others to access, view, and share online or via .jpgs using Buncee’s Download functionality. You grant each Buncee user and the public a personal, non-exclusive license to access, view, distribute and publicly display your public content. A private Buncee will not be posted to Buncee’s Latest Creations page or any of the Category pages, cannot be posted to any social media networks from the Buncee website, and cannot be shared via a public URL or embed code. When a Buncee is made private, you can email your Buncee to specified recipients via Buncee’s email functionality, share it via a private link., and save your Buncee as a .jpg using Buncee’s Download functionality. After creating a Buncee, you also have the option to make your Buncee "Copyable". By turning on this setting, you give other premium Buncee subscribers (i.e. bunceePLUS or bunceeEDU PLUS subscribers) complete permission to make a duplicate copy of your Buncee under his or her own profile, edit this Buncee copy along with it's contents and information, and / or alter it’s Post Settings including Category, Privacy, Comments and Copyable. Premium Buncee subscribers will not be able to alter or edit your original Buncee creation; they will only be able to alter or edit the duplicated copy of your Buncee. You also give other premium Buncee subscribers (i.e. bunceePLUS or bunceeEDU PLUS subscribers) complete permission to “Clip & Stitch” your Buncee. This means that any slide or multiple slides within the Copyable Buncee can be copied and used by other premium Buncee subscribers (i.e. bunceePLUS or bunceeEDU PLUS subscribers). Buncee subscribers will not be able to alter or edit your original Buncee slide(s); they will only be able to alter or edit the Clipped & Stitched copy of your Buncee slide(s). Your public Buncees set as Copyable can be duplicated by any premium Buncee subscriber. Your private Buncees set as Copyable can only be duplicated by any premium Buncee subscribers whom have received a copy of your Buncee via email. Buncees that are set as Copyable can also be used under our Clip & Stitch feature. Buncees set as Copyable can be Clipped & Stitched by any premium Buncee subscriber. Your private Buncees set as Copyable can only be Clipped & Stitched by any premium Buncee subscribers whom have received a copy of your Buncee via email. You can turn off and on the Copyable setting at any time, but any copies that were created during the time which it was set as Copyable cannot be revoked, unless provided herein. Please Note: Children who are under 13 years of age can subscribe to bunceeFREE accounts with verifiable parental consent. Please read our Privacy Policy to learn more about The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”), its rules, and our practices for collecting, using and disclosing personal information from children under the age of 13. 

bunceePLUS Users:

After creating a Buncee, you have the option to make your creation public or private. A public Buncee will be posted on the Latest Creations page and the corresponding Category page, and all of the content you create including all of the information within your Buncees will be available to anyone who has access to the internet. You have the option to email a public Buncee, post it to your favorite social media networks, share its public URL through any means, save it as a .jpg or PDF via Buncee’s Download functionality, or embed it on other websites or blogs. Public Buncees can be viewed by other Buncee users, will appear in the searchable Buncee database, and will be available for others to access, view, and share online and using Buncee's Download functionality. You grant each Buncee user and the public a personal, non-exclusive license to access, view, distribute and publicly display your public content. A private Buncee will not be posted to Buncee’s Latest Creations page or any of the Category pages, cannot be posted to any social media networks from the Buncee website, and cannot be shared via a public URL or embed code. When a Buncee is made private, you can email your Buncee to specified recipients via Buncee’s email functionality, share it via a private link, and save your Buncee as a .jpg or a PDF using Buncee’s Download functionality. After creating a Buncee, you also have the option to make your Buncee "Copyable". By turning on this setting, you give other premium Buncee subscribers (i.e. bunceePLUS or bunceeEDU PLUS subscribers) complete permission to make a duplicate copy of your Buncee under his or her own profile, edit this Buncee copy along with it's contents and information, and / or alter it’s Post Settings including Category, Privacy, Comments and Copyable. Premium Buncee subscribers will not be able to alter or edit your original Buncee creation; they will only be able to alter or edit the duplicated copy of your Buncee. You also give other premium Buncee subscribers (i.e. bunceePLUS or bunceeEDU PLUS subscribers) complete permission to “Clip & Stitch” your Buncee. This means that any slide or multiple slides within the Copyable Buncee can be copied and used by other premium Buncee subscribers (i.e. bunceePLUS or bunceeEDU PLUS subscribers). Buncee subscribers will not be able to alter or edit your original Buncee slide(s); they will only be able to alter or edit the Clipped & Stitched copy of your Buncee slide(s). Your public Buncees set as Copyable can be duplicated by any premium Buncee subscriber. Your private Buncees set as Copyable can only be duplicated by you - the bunceePLUS creator of the Buncee - or any premium Buncee subscribers whom have received a copy of your Buncee via email. Buncees that are set as Copyable can also be used under our Clip & Stitch feature. Buncees set as Copyable can be Clipped & Stitched by any premium Buncee subscriber. Your private Buncees set as Copyable can only be Clipped & Stitched by you - the bunceePLUS creator of the Buncee - or any premium Buncee subscribers whom have received a copy of your Buncee via email. You can turn off and on the Copyable setting at any time, but any copies that were created during the time which it was set as Copyable cannot be revoked, unless provided herein. Please Note: bunceePLUS accounts on [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/) are intended only for those who are at least 13 years old., and Buncee has no intention of collecting personal data from those under 13 years of age with respect to such accounts. 

edu.buncee.com accounts

bunceeEDU FREE Users:

Educators and students can subscribe to a bunceeEDU FREE account. After creating a Buncee, you have the option to make your creation public or private. A public Buncee will be posted on the corresponding Category page and all of the content you create in these public Buncees - including all of the information within them - will be available to anyone who has access to the internet. You have the option to email a public Buncee, post it to your favorite social media networks, share its public URL through any means, save it as a .jpg via Buncee’s Download functionality, or embed it on other websites or blogs. Public Buncees can be viewed by other bunceeEDU Users, will appear in the searchable bunceeEDU database, and will be available for others to access, view, and share online or via .jpgs using Buncee’s Download functionality. You grant each bunceeEDU user and the public a personal, non-exclusive license to access, view, distribute and publicly display your public content. A private Buncee will not be posted to Buncee’s Category pages, cannot be posted to any social media networks from the [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/). website, and cannot be shared via a public URL or embed code. When a Buncee is made private, you can email your Buncee to specified recipients via Buncee’s email functionality, share via a private link, and save your Buncee as a .jpg using Buncee’s Download functionality. After creating a Buncee, you also have the option to make your Buncee "Copyable". By turning on this setting, you give other premium Buncee subscribers (i.e. bunceePLUS or bunceeEDU PLUS subscribers) complete permission to make a duplicate copy of your Buncee under his or her own profile, edit this Buncee copy along with it's contents and information, and / or alter it’s Post Settings including Category, Privacy, Comments and Copyable. Premium Buncee subscribers will not be able to alter or edit your original Buncee creation; they will only be able to alter or edit the duplicated copy of your Buncee. You also give other premium Buncee subscribers (i.e. bunceePLUS or bunceeEDU PLUS subscribers) complete permission to “Clip & Stitch” your Buncee. This means that any slide or multiple slides within the Copyable Buncee can be copied and used by other premium Buncee subscribers (i.e. bunceePLUS or bunceeEDU PLUS subscribers). Buncee subscribers will not be able to alter or edit your original Buncee slide(s); they will only be able to alter or edit the Clipped & Stitched copy of your Buncee slide(s). Your public Buncees set as Copyable can be duplicated by any premium Buncee subscriber. Your private Buncees set as Copyable can only be duplicated by any premium Buncee subscribers whom have received a copy of your Buncee via email. Buncees that are set as Copyable can also be used under our Clip & Stitch feature. Buncees set as Copyable can be Clipped & Stitched by any premium Buncee subscriber. Your private Buncees set as Copyable can only be Clipped & Stitched by any premium Buncee subscribers whom have received a copy of your Buncee via email. You can turn off and on the Copyable setting at any time, but any copies that were created during the time which it was set as Copyable cannot be revoked, unless provided herein. Please Note: Students who are under 13 years of age can subscribe to bunceeEDU FREE student accounts with verifiable parental consent. BunceeEDU FREE teacher accounts are intended only for those who are at least 13 years old, and Buncee has no intention of collecting personal data from those under 13 years of age with respect to such accounts. Please read our Privacy Policy to learn more about The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”), its rules, and our practices for collecting, using and disclosing personal information from children under the age of 13. 

bunceeEDU PLUS Users:

An educator creates a bunceeEDU PLUS account and then creates sub-accounts on behalf of his/her students; and the Buncees created by these sub-account holders are private by default. By subscribing to bunceeEDU PLUS, an educator represents and warrants that he/she is either a teacher or school administrator, or otherwise authorized by a school or district to sign up on behalf of students, or that he/she is the parent or guardian of such student(s). When a teacher registers a student/child, he/she is creating a virtual classroom, and will do so without needing the contact information of that student/child. If you are a teacher, you represent and warrant that you have permission and authorization from your school and/or district to use Buncee as part of your curriculum. Before sharing, publishing, or allowing a student to share information such as personal photos, videos, or audio of the class, individuals, or groups of students, you represent and warrant that you have parental consent to use his/her child’s images/voice. By agreeing to our Terms and Privacy Policy, you, your school and/or district are responsible for the compliance to our Terms and Privacy Policy by you and your student sub-accounts, and for monitoring all content of your virtual classroom. This includes but is not limited to the following: 

  * Users are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any account information including passwords. You agree to notify Buncee immediately of any unauthorized use of your account or password, or any other security breach.
  * Users must not harass, threaten, impersonate, bully, or intimidate anyone.
  * Users must not upload, post, email, transmit, publicly perform, or otherwise make available any content that is unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, bullying, harassing, tortuous, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, libelous, invasive of another person’s privacy, hateful, or racially, ethically, or otherwise objectionable.
  * Users must not upload, post, email, transmit, publicly perform, or otherwise make available any content that violates the copyright, trademark, publicity, privacy, or other rights of third parties.

Student sub-accounts are created by the teacher, and do not require contact information of that student/child. We will not knowingly use or distribute personal data from students. All Buncees created under the student sub-account are private by default, and are only be visible to the teacher. The teacher has the ability to make student submissions public with each assignment, which allows students to share their Buncees via email or embed. All Buncees created under the student sub-accounts do not have the option to share their Buncees via social media networks, and their creations will not be posted on the Latest Creations page or any Category pages. All Buncees created by the teacher (bunceeEDU PLUS account holder) have the option to be made private or public. A private Buncee will be visible to the teacher’s students when submitted as an assignment. A private Buncee will not be posted on any of the Category pages or the Educational Resources page, cannot be posted to any social media networks from the [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/) website, and cannot be shared via a public URL or embed code. When a Buncee is made private, you can email your Buncee to specified recipients via Buncee’s email functionality, share the private link, and save your Buncee as a .jpg or a PDF using Buncee’s Download functionality. BunceeEDU PLUS account holders do have the ability to make their own educator Buncees public. A public Buncee will be posted on the corresponding Category page, can be posted on the Educational Resources page, and all of the content created including all of the information within your public Buncees will be available to anyone who has access to the internet. BunceeEDU account holders also have the ability to make their student submissions, or groups of student submissions public. Student submissions are private by default, but can be made public by the educator on an assignment by assignment basis. You have the option to email a public Buncee, post it to your favorite social media networks, share its public URL through any means, save it as a .jpg or PDF using Buncee’s Download Functionality or embed it on other websites or blogs. Public Buncees can be viewed by other bunceeEDU FREE and bunceeEDU PLUS users, will appear in the searchable bunceeEDU database, and will be available for others to access, view, and share online. You grant each bunceeEDU FREE and bunceeEDU PLUS user and the public a personal, non-exclusive license to access, view, distribute and publicly display your public content. All Buncees created by the educator (bunceeEDU PLUS account holder) can be set as “Copyable”. A Copyable Buncee gives other premium Buncee subscribers (bunceeEDU PLUS or bunceePLUS subscribers) complete permission to copy such Buncees into his or her own profile, edit this Buncee copy along with it's contents and information, and / or alter it’s Post Settings including Education Level, Category, Privacy, Comments and Copyable. Premium Buncee subscribers will not be able to alter or edit the educator’s original Buncee creation; they will only be able to alter or edit the duplicated copy of the educator’s Buncee. You also give other premium Buncee subscribers (i.e. bunceePLUS or bunceeEDU PLUS subscribers) complete permission to “Clip & Stitch” your Buncee. This means that any slide or multiple slides within the Copyable Buncee can be copied and used by other premium Buncee subscribers (i.e. bunceePLUS or bunceeEDU PLUS subscribers). Buncee subscribers will not be able to alter or edit your original Buncee slide(s); they will only be able to alter or edit the Clipped & Stitched copy of your Buncee slide(s). The educator’s public Buncees set as Copyable can be duplicated by any premium Buncee subscriber, or by their student sub-accounts. This educator’s private Buncees set as Copyable can only be copied by the educator himself / herself, any recipients receiving the Buncee via Buncee’s email functionality, or by the student sub-accounts if submitted by the educator as an assignment. Buncees that are set as Copyable can also be used under our Clip & Stitch feature. Buncees set as Copyable can be Clipped & Stitched by any premium Buncee subscriber. Your private Buncees set as Copyable can only be Clipped & Stitched by you - the bunceePLUS creator of the Buncee - or any premium Buncee subscribers whom have received a copy of your Buncee via email. You can turn off and on the Copyable setting at any time, but any copies that were created during the time which it was set as Copyable cannot be revoked, unless provided herein. Student sub-accounts created under the educator bunceeEDU PLUS only have the ability to copy their teacher’s assignment when the teacher makes the assignment copyable. They do not have the ability to copy any other teacher or student Buncees. Furthermore, any Buncees created by the student sub-accounts cannot be set as Copyable. However, any Buncees created by the student sub-accounts can be copied or clipped & stitched by their main teacher account through assignment submission or email. Please Note: Only educators are allowed to subscribe themselves and their classrooms to a bunceeEDU PLUS account. Buncee has no intention of collecting personal data from those under 13 years of age with respect to such accounts. 

bunceeEDU Schools Users:

A school or district administrator enables the edu.buncee application through Google Classroom or Clever. Teacher and student accounts are created by syncing Google Classroom roster data with Buncee, or by using the SIS sync powered by Clever. The school or district administrator controls all creation and sharing options for the district, school(s), user type(s), and/or user(s). By subscribing to bunceeEDU Schools, an administrator represents and warrants that he/she is authorized by a school or district to sign up on behalf of students. When an administrator registers a school or district, they will be issued a URL that is unique to that school or district. You, the administrator, represents and warrants that you have permission and authorization from the school and/or district to use Buncee as part of your curriculum. Before sharing, publishing, or allowing a student to share information such as personal photos, videos, or audio of the class, individuals, or groups of students, you represent and warrant that you have parental consent to use his/her child’s images/voice. By agreeing to our Terms and Privacy Policy, you, your school and/or district are responsible for the compliance to our Terms and Privacy Policy by you, the teachers, and the students, and for monitoring all content of your school or district. This includes but is not limited to the following: 

  * Users are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any account information including passwords. You agree to notify Buncee immediately of any unauthorized use of your account or password, or any other security breach.
  * Users must not harass, threaten, impersonate, bully, or intimidate anyone.
  * Users must not upload, post, email, transmit, publicly perform, or otherwise make available any content that is unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, bullying, harassing, tortuous, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, libelous, invasive of another person’s privacy, hateful, or racially, ethically, or otherwise objectionable.
  * Users must not upload, post, email, transmit, publicly perform, or otherwise make available any content that violates the copyright, trademark, publicity, privacy, or other rights of third parties.

bunceeEDU has chosen Google Classroom and Clever as a data integration partners. Teacher and student accounts are setup by syncing Google Classroom roster data with Buncee, or via Clever using Secure Sync. Google Classroom and Clever will sync class rosters with Google Classroom or Clever-enabled applications. Google Classroom’s Terms of Service and Privacy Policy can be viewed here. Clever’s Terms of Service and Privacy Policy can be viewed here. We will not knowingly use or distribute personal data from students. All Buncees created under the student accounts are private by default, and can be shared via assignment submission, email, and/or embed. A district or school administrator can disable or enable any form of public sharing at their discretion. By default, all Buncees created under the student sub-accounts do not have the option to share their Buncees via social media networks, and their creations will not be posted on a Latest Creations page or any Category pages. All Buncees created by the teacher have the option to be made private or public. A private Buncee will be visible to the teacher’s students when submitted as an assignment. A private Buncee will not be posted on any Category pages or Educational Resources page, cannot be posted to any social media networks from the [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/) website, and cannot be shared via a public URL or embed code. When a Buncee is made private, you can email your Buncee to specified recipients via Buncee’s email functionality, share the private link, and save your Buncee as a .jpg or a PDF using Buncee’s Download functionality. Teacher accounts do have the ability to make their own educator Buncees public. A district or school administrator can disable any form of public sharing at their discretion. A public Buncee can be posted on an Educational Resources page, and all of the content created including all of the information within your public Buncees will be available to anyone who has access to the internet. By default, you have the option to email a public Buncee, post it to your favorite social media networks, share its public URL through any means, save it as a .jpg or PDF using Buncee’s Download Functionality or embed it on other websites or blogs. Public Buncees may be able to be viewed by other bunceeEDU users and may be available for others to access, view, and share online. You grant each bunceeEDU user and the public a personal, non-exclusive license to access, view, distribute and publicly display your public content. All Buncees created by the educator can be set as “Copyable”. A Copyable Buncee gives other premium Buncee subscribers within the school or district, complete permission to copy such Buncees into his or her own profile, edit this Buncee copy along with it's contents and information, and / or alter it’s Post Settings including Education Level, Category, Privacy, Comments and Copyable. Premium Buncee subscribers within the school or district will not be able to alter or edit the educator’s original Buncee creation; they will only be able to alter or edit the duplicated copy of the educator’s Buncee. Buncees that are set as Copyable can also be used under our Clip & Stitch feature. Buncees set as Copyable can be Clipped & Stitched by other premium subscribers within the school or district. Your private Buncees set as Copyable can only be Clipped & Stitched by you - the creator of the Buncee - or any premium Buncee subscribers within the school or district whom have received a copy of your Buncee via email. You can turn off and on the Copyable setting at any time, but any copies that were created during the time which it was set as Copyable cannot be revoked, unless provided herein. Student accounts created under the educator only have the ability to copy their teacher’s assignment when the teacher makes the assignment copyable. They do not have the ability to copy any other teacher or student Buncees. Furthermore, any Buncees created by the student sub-accounts cannot be set as Copyable. However, any Buncees created by the student sub-accounts can be copied or clipped & stitched by their main teacher account through assignment submission or email. Please Note: Only district or school administrators are allowed to subscribe to a bunceeEDU Schools account, which is intended only for those who are at least 13 years old, and Buncee has no intention of collecting personal data from those under 13 years of age with respect to such accounts. 

Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool (iOS App)

Educators and students can create a bunceeEDU FREE account through its mobile application, Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool. A bunceeEDU PLUS account or a bunceeEDU Schools account must be created on the web, but users can then access the Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool app using those credentials. You must access your Buncee creation on our web version, on either [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/) or <https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools> in order to change any of your Buncee settings such as public/private, commenting on/off, copyable on/off, as well as to make a Buncee an assignment. As such, any Buncee created in a bunceeEDU Schools account will reflect the creation permissions established by the school/district. Any Buncee created on the mobile application will be stored in your account located on our cloud-based website on either [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/) or <https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools>. In addition, an account created on the mobile application can only be upgraded to a bunceeEDU PLUS account by visiting the website at [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/) and clicking to upgrade. (please see **bunceeEDU PLUS Users** for the full description of PLUS’ additional functionality) By default, any Buncee created within the mobile app is private. Any Buncee created in a bunceeEDU Schools account will reflect the creation permissions established by the school/district. Sharing functionality is dependent on the applications installed on each individual device, and is therefore tied to the iOS device being used by the teacher or student. We recommend that devices utilized in the classroom have applications installed which offer teachers and students appropriate methods to share their Buncee creations. Please Note: Students who are under 13 years of age can subscribe individually to Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool with verifiable parental consent. Buncee has no intention of collecting personal data from those under 13 years of age with respect to such accounts. Student subaccounts which are subscribed to [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/) under a bunceeEDU PLUS Teacher account, or a bunceeEDU Schools account, can access the mobile application, Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool using the login credentials provided by their teacher. Please read our Privacy Policy to learn more about The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”), its rules, and our practices for collecting, using and disclosing personal information from children under the age of 13. 

Safety

Buncee uses their best efforts to be safe and sound, but this cannot be guaranteed. You commit to Buncee that you will not abuse or misuse Buncee services specifically, you represent you will not participate, including but not limited to uploading, posting, emailing, inmailing, or transmitting the following: 

  * Unauthorized commercial communications;
  * Access of Buncee through automated means without consent of Buncee;
  * Engage in unlawful practices;
  * Upload viruses or other malicious content;
  * Access an account of another;
  * Intimidate, discriminate, or harass any user or recipient of communications via [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), <https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools>, or its mobile applications;
  * Post hateful, threatening or pornographic content;
  * Create a Buncee containing alcohol-related mature content without appropriate age based restrictions;
  * Create a Buncee containing drug-related mature content;
  * Offer any promotion on Buncee without prior written consent;
  * Use or access Buncee if you are less than thirteen years of age;
  * Use the Buncee site services or tools if you are not able to form a legally binding contract;
  * Harvest or otherwise collect information about users including email addresses, without their consent;
  * Adapt, modify or create derivative works based on Buncee or technology underlying the Services, or other User's content, in whole or part, except as permitted under Buncee’s developer program;
  * Use manual or automated software, devices, scripts, robots, other means or processes to access, "scrape," "crawl" or "spider" any web pages or other services contained in the site;
  * Attempt to or actually override any security component included in or underlying Buncee;
  * Remove any copyright, trademark or other proprietary rights notices contained in or on Buncee, including those of both Buncee and any of its licensors; Use or attempt to use another's account without authorization from the Company, or create a false identity on Buncee;
  * Falsely state, impersonate or otherwise misrepresent your identity;
  * Add to a content field content that is not intended for such field;
  * Include information that you do not have the right to disclose or make available under any law or under any contractual or fiduciary relationships;
  * Infringe upon patents, trademarks, trade secrets, copyrights or other proprietary rights;
  * Forge headers or otherwise manipulate identifiers in order to disguise the origin of any communication transmitted through the Services;
  * Take any action that violates the law or violates or infringes someone else’s rights, including posting sensitive information on Buncee;
  * Tag users without their consent.
  * You agree to the following sign in criteria:
  * Keep your password secure and confidential;
  * Do not permit others to use your account;
  * Refrain from using other Users’ accounts;
  * Refrain from selling, trading, or otherwise transferring your Buncee account to another party; and
  * Refrain from charging anyone for access to any portion of Buncee, or any information therein.

Further, you are responsible for anything that happens through your account until you close down your account or prove that your account security was compromised due to no fault of your own. To close your account, please use the deactivate function found on your user profile page. 

Release

You indemnify us and hold us harmless for all damages, losses and costs (including, but not limited to, reasonable attorneys’ fees and costs) related to all claims, charges, and investigations, caused by: 

  * Your failure to comply with this Section as well as this entire Agreement, including, without limitation, your submission of content that violates third party rights or applicable laws;
  * Any content you submit to the Services;
  * Any activity in which you engage on or through Buncee.

If you have a dispute with one or more users, you indemnify us (and our officers, directors, agents, subsidiaries, joint ventures and employees) from claims, demands and damages (actual and consequential) of every kind and nature, known and unknown, arising out of, or in any way connected with, such disputes. You will resolve any claim, cause of action or dispute ("claim") you have with us arising out of, or relating to, this Agreement or Buncee exclusively in a state or federal court located in Suffolk County, New York. New York State Law will govern you and us, without regard to conflict of law provisions. You agree to submit to the personal jurisdiction of the courts located in Suffolk County, New York for the purpose of litigating all such claims. If anyone brings a claim against us related to your actions, content or information on Buncee, you will indemnify and hold us harmless from and against all damages, losses, and expenses of any kind (including reasonable legal fees and costs) related to such claim. 

Notifications

For purposes of service messages and notices about the Services to you, notice shall consist of an email from Buncee to an email address associated with your account, even if we have other contact information. You also agree that Buncee may communicate with you through your Buncee account or through other means including email, mobile number, telephone, or delivery services including the US Postal Service about your Buncee account or services associated with Buncee. You acknowledge and agree that we shall have no liability associated with or arising from your failure to maintain accurate contact or other information, including, but not limited to, your failure to receive critical information about the Service. 

Protecting Rights

You authorize Buncee to remove any content or information you post on Buncee if Buncee believes in its sole discretion that it violates this User Agreement. Additionally, Buncee may, in its sole discretion, alert educators, authorities and/or other parties with respect to any content or information posted on Buncee that Buncee believes in its sole discretion violates this Agreement or otherwise creates a risk or a possible legal exposure to Buncee, Buncee Users or recipients. 

Mobile Application

Buncee may offer the Services through mobile applications created by it or third party developers ("Platform Developers"). If you use the Services through a mobile device, you agree that all information about your use of the Services through your mobile device and carrier may be communicated to us. By accessing the Services using a mobile device, you represent that to the extent you import any of your Buncee data to your mobile device that you have authority to share the transferred data with your mobile carrier or other access provider. In the event you change or deactivate your mobile account, you must, before you use Buncee, update your Buncee account information to ensure that your messages are not sent to the person that acquires your old number and failure to do so is your responsibility. You are responsible for all charges. 

Export Control Laws

Using Buncee is subject to export and re-export control laws and regulations and required authorizations. You warrant that you are not prohibited from receiving US origin products, including services or software. 

Provisions Applying to Developers or Operations of Applications and Websites

If you are a developer or operator of a Platform application or website, the following additional terms apply to you: You are responsible for your application and its content and all uses you make of the Platform. Your access to and use of data you receive from Buncee will be by Separate Written Agreement between you and Buncee. 

User Rights

If Buncee considers that you have abided by all your obligations, express or implied, under this User Agreement, Buncee grants to you a limited, revocable, nonexclusive, nonassignable, nonsublicenseable right to access, through a generally available web browser or mobile device or application (but not through scraping, spidering, crawling or other technology or software used to access data without the express written consent of Buncee), view information and use the Services that we provide. We reserve all rights not expressly granted in this Agreement, including, without limitation, title, ownership, intellectual property rights, and all other rights and interest in Buncee and all related items. 

Additional Buncee Rights and Obligations

Buncee allows you to access Buncee as it may exist and be available on any given day and has no other obligations, except as expressly stated in this Agreement. We may modify, replace, refuse access to, suspend or discontinue in our sole discretion effective upon the posting on our site or by direct communication to you. Buncee may include links to third party web sites. You are responsible for the consequences of access or use of a Third Party Site or Platform Application. You acknowledge, consent and agree that we may access, preserve, and disclose your registration, and any other information you provide, if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary in our opinion to: 

  * comply with legal process;
  * enforce this Agreement;
  * respond to claims of a violation of the rights of third parties, whether or not the third party is a User, individual, or government agency;
  * respond to customer service inquiries; or
  * protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Buncee, our Users or the public.

You are solely responsible for your interactions with other Users. Buncee may limit the number of Buncees you may share with other Users; or prohibit you from contacting other Users through use of the Services. Buncee reserves the right, but has no obligation, to monitor disputes between you and other members and to restrict, suspend, or close your account if Buncee determines, in our sole discretion, that doing so is necessary to enforce this Agreement. 

Changes to these Terms of Service

We reserve the right to modify this statement of terms at any time, so please review it. You agree to accept notice of the change by posting here on Buncee or by your use of Buncee. 

Termination

Buncee reserves the right to terminate services to your account if Buncee believes you violated this Agreement or otherwise created a risk or a possible legal exposure to Buncee, Buncee Users, or recipients. You may terminate this Agreement, for any or no reason, at any time, with notice to Buncee. This notice will be effective upon Buncee processing your notice. Buncee may terminate the Agreement for any reason or no reason, at any time, with or without notice. This cancellation shall be effective immediately, or as may be specified in the notice. Upon the termination of your Buncee account, you lose access to the Services, and Buncee may block access to the Services from an IP address or range of IP addresses associated with those of terminated Users. 

New York Law

Any disputes, claims or litigation regarding Buncee shall be governed by New York State Law regardless of your country of origin or where you access Buncee, and notwithstanding of any conflicts of law principles. 

Severability

This statement makes up the entire agreement between the parties regarding Buncee, and supersedes any prior agreements. If any portion of this Agreement is found to be unenforceable, the remaining portion will remain in full force and effect. If we fail to enforce any of this Statement, it will not be considered a waiver. All of our rights and obligations under this statement are freely assignable by us in connection with a merger, acquisition, or sale of assets, or by operation of law or otherwise. Nothing in this Agreement shall prevent us from complying with the law. 

Privacy Policy for Buncee LLC

Thanks for your interest in Buncee LLC’s online and mobile services. This Agreement sets forth the Privacy Policy which applies to any individual accessing [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com/schools](https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools)***, and/or our mobile applications Buncee Bits, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool, all hereinafter referred to as “Buncee”. Before signing up at [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com/schools](https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools), or buncee's mobile apps, we request that you read and accept our User Agreement which consists of this Privacy Policy (Policy) and our Terms and Conditions (Terms). This Policy explains what personal information we collect, why we collect it, and how it is used. If you have any questions regarding this Policy or the Terms, please contact us at [privacy@buncee.com](mailto:privacy@buncee.com). *** <https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools> is our Buncee for Schools and Districts product. Each district is supplied with it’s own private domain, i.e. yourdistrict.edu.buncee.com and an administrative dashboard, i.e. yourdistrict.admin.edu.buncee.com. 

Information Collection & User Registration

In order to use this website, you must first complete the registration form and create a username and password. During registration, you are required to give contact information (such as name and email address), gender, and date of birth. We will use your contact information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. Please Note: Under a bunceeEDU PLUS subscription, student sub-accounts can only be created by subscribers of the bunceeEDU PLUS plan, and do not require the submission of email, gender or birth data. Under a bunceeEDU Schools subscription, student accounts are created by syncing Google Classroom roster data with Buncee, or by using the SIS sync powered by Clever, and do not require the submission of email, gender or birth data. Both Google Classroom and Clever syncs class rosters with Google Classroom or Clever-enabled applications. You can view Google Classroom’s [Terms of Service](https://www.google.com/policies/terms/) and [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). You can view Clever’s [Terms of Service](https://clever.com/about/terms) and [Privacy Policy](https://clever.com/about/privacy-policy). Buncee LLC is the sole owner of [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com/schools](https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools), and/or our mobile applications Buncee Bits, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool, and any information collected on [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com/schools](https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools), and/or our mobile applications Buncee Bits, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool, including personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our website. If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information, such as name, email, and financial information such as credit card number and expiration date. We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. When you place an order, you will receive an email from Paypal or Stripe if it was your chosen payment option. Please see our Payment Terms for additional details. Surveys or Contests: From time-to-time, we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary. Therefore, you have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic information (such as zip code). We will communicate with you through email and notices posted on the [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com/schools](https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools), and/or our mobile applications Buncee Bits, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool, or through other means available through the service. We may send you a series of emails that help inform Users about the features of the service, and we will also send you service messages relating to the functioning of the Services. We may also send you messages with promotional information directly or on behalf of our agents, unless you have opted out of receiving promotional information. Please Note: Under a bunceeEDU PLUS subscription or a bunceeEDU Schools subscription,, student sub-accounts will not receive promotional communications from Buncee or our agents. Further, children that are under 13 years of age with subscriptions to bunceeFREE or bunceeEDU FREE student accounts will not receive promotional communications from Buncee or our agents. Many communications you initiate through [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com/schools](https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools), and/or our mobile applications Buncee Bits, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool, (e.g. an invitation sent to a non-User) will list your primary email address and the name of the message. Other communications that you initiate through the [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com/schools](https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools) website, and/or our mobile applications Buncee Bits, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool, like a request for an introduction, will list your name as the initiator, but will not include your personal email address contact information. Your contact information will only be shared with another User if both of you have indicated that you would like to establish contact with each other. If you have questions or concerns, email us at [privacy@buncee.com](mailto:privacy@buncee.com). 

Uses of Information

Personal Information Collected:

We collect information: 

  * When you register an account to become a [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), an [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com/schools](https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools) user (“User”), and/or a User of our mobile applications Buncee Bits, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool, such as your name, email, birthdate, and a password. Please Note: Under a bunceeEDU PLUS subscription, student accounts can only be created by subscribers of the bunceeEDU PLUS plan, and do not require the submission of email, gender or birth data. Under a bunceeEDU Schools subscription, teacher and student accounts are created by syncing Google Classroom roster data with Buncee or by using the SIS sync powered by Clever. Further, except as set forth in the ‘Children Under the Age of 13’ section, personally identifiable information such as contact information, gender or birth data submitted on Buncee by anyone under 13 violates our Terms and Conditions and will not be accepted.
  * When you add to your profile with further information about yourself or your private contacts, join or post to [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com/schools](https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools), or our mobile applications Buncee Bits, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool groups, answers and other member to member communication. We have access to your internet user information, like your IP address, the URLs of sites from which you arrive or leave [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), or [edu.buncee.com/schools](https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools), your type of browser, your operating system, your mobile provider, your mobile device, and your ISP through tools like Google Analytics. To learn more about the privacy policy of Google Analytics, click [here](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/), and to learn how to opt out of that service click [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)c.

Uses of Personal Information:

We use the information you provide to: 

  * Enable you to share your information and communicate with other Users, or provide your personal details to third parties offering combined services with [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com/schools](https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools), and/or our mobile applications Buncee Bits, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool.
  * Administer your account with us and customize the service we provide to you and other Users; and to
  * Send you service or promotional communications through email and notices on the [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), or [edu.buncee.com/schools](https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools) websites, and/or our mobile applications Buncee Bits, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool. Please Note: Under a bunceeEDU PLUS subscription or bunceeEDU Schools subscription,, student sub-accounts will not receive promotional communications from Buncee or our agents. Further, children that are under 13 years of age with subscriptions to bunceeFREE or bunceeEDU FREE student accounts will not receive promotional communications from Buncee or our agents.

We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties for marketing purposes. We also provide you with the means to control whether or not your profile is viewable to other Users. Student sub-accounts created by a bunceeEDU PLUS subscriber or a bunceeEDU Schools subscriber are private by default and will only be visible to the subscriber, not to other Users. Please note that in order to deliver certain services, we may share information with third parties. Please note that for children under 13 years of age, no third party service providers have access to children’s data. 

Your Information Choices:

You can: 

  * Review, enhance, or edit your personal information through your personal profile page;
  * Control the messages you receive from Buncee and other Users;
  * Change your setting to control visibility and accessibility through our website; and
  * Tell us to close your Buncee account.

Your Obligation to Other Users: Do not abuse the [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), or [edu.buncee.com/schools](https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools), and/or our mobile applications Buncee Bits, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool, by using it to spam, abuse, harass, threaten or otherwise violate the User Agreement or Privacy Policy. Buncee reserves the right to suspend or terminate the account of any User that violates the User Agreement or Privacy Policy. 

Security:

  * Personal information you provide will be secured with industry standards and technology. Since the Internet is not a 100% secure environment, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com/schools](https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools), and/or our mobile applications Buncee Bits, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool. There is no guarantee that information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical or managerial safeguards. If you have questions about security on our website, you can email us at [security@buncee.com](mailto:security@buncee.com).
  * When you purchase an account, we have security measures in place and take reasonable precautions to protect against the loss, misuse and unauthorized access of personal information under our control.
  * You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information and for controlling access to your email communications at all times.

Communications from the Site

Service-related Announcements:

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. Please Note: Under a bunceeEDU PLUS subscription or a bunceeEDU Schools subscription,, student sub-accounts will not receive service-related announcements from Buncee. Further, children that are under 13 years of age with subscriptions to bunceeFREE or bunceeEDU FREE student accounts will not receive promotional communications from Buncee or our agents. 

Customer Service:

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you an activation and welcome email. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. Please Note: Under a bunceeEDU PLUS subscription or a bunceeEDU Schools subscription,, student sub-accounts will not receive an activation or welcome email from Buncee. Further, children that are under 13 years of age with subscriptions to bunceeFREE or bunceeEDU FREE student accounts will not receive an activation or welcome email from Buncee. Should a student sub-account have a customer service related issue, they should contact the subscriber of the bunceeEDU PLUS plan or the subscriber of the bunceeEDU Schools plan . Should a child have a customer service related issue, they should contact the parent or guardian whom initiated the parental consent form. Should the child or student sub-account reach out to Buncee via live chat, email or telephone, any information collected will be for the sole purpose of resolving the customer service related issue. If we know that the child or student is under the age of 13, we will not knowingly keep personally identifiable information that is unintentionally included in the student’s inquiry, and any such information will be deleted after their inquiry/issue has been resolved. 

Profile:

We store information that we collect through log files and/or third party sources to create a “profile” of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information, and your purchasing history, to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you. We share this collected data in anonymized form only. Information Sharing and Disclosure Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable): We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users; rather this information identifies usage of the site by Zip Code. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information. 

Personally Identifiable Information

Service Providers:

We use other third parties to provide services on our site. When you sign up, we will share information as necessary for the third party to provide that service. Please note that for children under 13 years of age, no third party service providers have access to children’s data. 

Legal Disclaimer:

It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information, profile information, and/or information about your activities as a [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com/schools](https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools) User, and/or a User of our mobile applications Buncee Bits, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool, when required by subpoena or other legal process, or if Buncee has a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to 

  * investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities or to assist government enforcement agencies;
  * to enforce the User Agreement, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third party claims or allegations, or to protect the security or integrity of our site; and/or c. to exercise or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our Users, employees, or others.

Links to Other Sites:

Buncee, LLC may contain links to or allow you to interact with and make use of other independent third-party websites, products or services ("Third-Party Sites, Products and Services"). Access to Third-Party Sites, Products and Services is provided solely as a convenience to our visitors. Such Third-Party Sites, Products and Services are not under Buncee LLC’s control and Buncee LLC does not necessarily endorse the content, advertising, products, services or other materials on or available from such Third-Party Sites, Products and Services. Your use of any Third-Party Sites, Products and Services may be subject to the third-party provider's terms and conditions and privacy policy and may involve the disclosure or transfer of information from or about you to the third-party provider. You will need to make your own independent judgment regarding your use of and interaction with any Third-Party Sites, Products and Services. You acknowledge and agree that Buncee LLC is not responsible for the availability of any Third-Party Sites, Products and Services and that Buncee LLC shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with your use of or interaction with any Third-Party Sites, Products and Services. 

Access to Personally Identifiable Information:

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on your profile page or by emailing our Customer Support at [info@buncee.com](mailto:info@buncee.com) or call us at 631-591-1390. 

Security:

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at [security@buncee.com](mailto:security@buncee.com). 

Business Transitions:

In the event Buncee LLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger, consolidation, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via a prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

Children Under the Age of 13:

The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and its rules (collectively, “COPPA”) require us to inform parents and legal guardians (as used in this section, “parents”) and teachers, administrators, schools, districts and other educators (as used in this section, “educators”) about our practices for collecting, using and disclosing personal information from children under the age of 13 (“children” or “child”). It also requires us to obtain verifiable consent from a child’s parent for certain collection, use and disclosure of the child’s personal information. For more information on COPPA, please click [here](https://www.ftc.gov/enforcement/rules/rulemaking-regulatory-reform-proceedings/childrens-online-privacy-protection-rule). This section notifies parents and educators of: 

  * The types of information we may collect from children.
  * Our practices for notifying parents/educators and obtaining consent when we collect personal information from children.
  * How we use the information we collect.
  * Our practices for disclosing that information.
  * How parents/educators can access and correct children’s personal information, including how a parent/educator may revoke consent.
  * All third party operators through which children may disclose personal information.

This section only applies to children under the age of 13 and supplements the other provisions of this Privacy Policy. Except as set forth in this section, personally identifiable information such as contact information, gender or birth data submitted on Buncee by anyone under 13 violates our Terms and Conditions and will not be accepted. Children may register for a bunceeFREE account on [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), a bunceeFREE student account on [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), and a Buncee Student account on our mobile application Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool (“Child Accounts”) with verifiable parental consent.. BunceePLUS accounts on [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/) and bunceeEDU FREE teacher accounts on [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/) are intended only for those who are at least 13 years old, and Buncee has no intention of collecting personal data from those under 13 years of age with respect to such accounts. In addition, only educators and schools/districts are allowed to subscribe to a bunceeEDU PLUS account or a bunceeEDU Schools account, and are intended only for those who are at least 13 years old; however, educators who subscribe to a bunceeEDU PLUS account may create student sub-accounts for their students (“Student Sub-accounts”). If an educator subscribes to a bunceeEDU PLUS account and registers a student under a Student Sub-account, it is the responsibility of the subscriber to monitor the content within the bunceeEDU PLUS account and abide by Buncee’s Terms and Conditions. Only school or district administrators are allowed to subscribe to a bunceeEDU Schools account. Teacher and student accounts are created by syncing Google Classroom roster data with Buncee, or by using the SIS sync powered by Clever. It is the responsibility of the subscriber to monitor the content within the bunceeEDU Schools account and abide by Buncee’s Terms and Conditions. We understand and are committed to respecting and protecting children’s privacy online. However, we urge parents and educators to instruct their children/students to never give out their real names, addresses, phone numbers, or any other information that would allow someone to identify or contact the child. If you believe that your child/student has gained access to Buncee without your consent, or if you have any questions or concerns, please contact us at [privacy@buncee.com](mailto:privacy@buncee.com). Additionally, in our commitment to protect the privacy of children, Buncee participates in the iKeepSafe Safe Harbor program. If you have any questions or need to file a complaint related to our privacy policy and practices, please contact the iKeepSafe Safe Harbor program’s dedicated consumer complaint department at [COPPAPrivacy@ikeepsafe.org](mailto:COPPAPrivacy@ikeepsafe). 

Information We Collect from Children:

While children can access certain parts of Buncee without providing us with personal information, most content and features are available only to registered users and require us to collect certain information, including personal information, from them. In addition, we use certain technologies, such as cookies, to automatically collect information from our users (including children) when they visit or use Buncee. We only collect as much information about a child as is reasonably necessary for the child to participate in an activity, and we do not condition his or her participation on the disclosure of more personal information than is reasonably necessary. 

Information We Collect Directly:

A child must provide us with the following information to register for Child Accounts: the child’s first name, last name, date of birth, and a parent’s email address. We also require the child to create a username and password. We may request additional information from your child, but this information is optional. We specify whether information is required or optional where we request it. When an educator registers a child under a Student Sub-account, the following information will be provided about the child by the educator: the child’s first name and last name, as well as a username and password. When a district or school administrator registers for a bunceeEDU Schools account, student accounts are created by syncing Google Classroom roster data with Buncee, or by using the SIS sync powered by Clever, and automatically pull in the child’s first name, last name, username, and password. Parents must complete the registration process for their children with respect to Child Accounts, and educators must complete the registration process for their students with respect to Student Sub-accounts. When we receive a request from a child to register for a Child Account or from a district/school or an educator to register a child for a Student Sub-account, we will provide direct notice (the “COPPA Notice”) to the parent, administrator, or educator, as applicable, via email in accordance with COPPA to, among other things, notify the parent/administrator/educator (a) that, with respect to Child Accounts, we have collected the parent’s online contact information and the child’s name from the child for the purpose of getting the parent’s consent to collect, use or disclose personal information from the child; (b) that verifiable consent from the parent is required for Buncee’s collection, use or disclosure of the child’s personal information; (c) that Buncee will not collect, use or disclose personal information from the child if the parent does not provide consent; (d) what additional personal information we intend to collect from the child and how we may disclose the information to others; (e) how the parent/educator can access this Privacy Policy; (f) how the parent can give verifiable consent; and (g) that if the parent does not give consent within a reasonable time, we will delete the parent’s and child’s online contact information from our records. Before the collection, use or disclosure of personal information from children, we will request verifiable consent from parents. To provide us with verifiable consent, the parent must, among other requirements, (a) click on the registration verification link contained in the COPPA Notice; (b) provide or confirm information, including limited, basic, personal information about themselves and their children, as prompted by our registration processes; (c) agree to abide by our Terms and Conditions and to ensure that any use of Buncee by their children does not violate our Terms and Conditions; (d) review and edit their child’s username to ensure that no personally identifiable information is present in the child’s username; (e) review and consent to Buncee’s practices with respect to collecting and using personal information from children under 13 as specified in the COPPA Notice and this Privacy Policy; and (f) print and sign our consent form and return it to us by (1) mailing the signed consent form to Buncee LLC, SBU Calverton Business Incubator, 4603 Middle Country Road, Calverton, NY 11933, (2) faxing the signed consent form to 631-591-1389, or (3) scanning and emailing the signed consent form to [privacy@buncee.com](mailto:privacy@buncee.com). Children may not use Buncee until we receive and process this verifiable consent. If we determine that a user is under 13 and we have not received a signed consent form from this child’s parent, we will take steps to delete all or virtually all content posted by the user and take reasonable technical measures to delete all or virtually all stored user information about the user from our records, in compliance with applicable laws. Please Note: Where a district/school administrator or an educator registers its students for Student Sub-accounts, we will not obtain verifiable consent directly from parents, and will presume that the district/school administrator’s or educator’s registration for such accounts and authorization for the collection, use and disclosure of students’ personal information is based upon the district/school administrator or educator having obtained the parents’ consent. In this regard, the district/school administrator or educator will act as the parent’s agent and consent to the collection, use and disclosure of children’s personal information on the parent’s behalf. Further, before sharing, publishing, or allowing a student to share information such as personal photos, videos, or audio of the class, individuals, or groups of students, the district/school administrator or educator represents and warrants that the school has acquired parental consent to use his/her child’s images/voice. In addition, it is the responsibility of the district/school administrator or educator to comply with its obligations under COPPA, the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (“FERPA”) and the Protection of Pupil Rights Amendment (“PPRA”), as well as all relevant state laws, with respect to its collection, use and disclosure of personal information from children. For more information on COPPA, please click [here](https://www.ftc.gov/enforcement/rules/rulemaking-regulatory-reform-proceedings/childrens-online-privacy-protection-rule), and for more information on FERPA and PPRA, please click [here](http://ptac.ed.gov/). 

Automatic Information Collection and Tracking:

We use technology to automatically collect information from our users, including children, when they access and navigate through Buncee and use certain of its features. The information we collect through these technologies may include: 

  * One or more persistent identifiers that can be used to recognize a user over time and across different websites and online services (including your internet user information, like your IP address, the URLs of sites from which you arrive or leave [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), your type of browser, your operating system, your mobile provider, your mobile device, and your ISP through tools like Google Analytics).
  * Information that identifies a device’s location (geolocation information).

We also may combine non-personal information we collect through these technologies with personal information about you or your child that we collect online. For information about our automatic information collection practices, including how you can opt out of certain information collection, see the “Personal Information Collected” and “Your Information Choices” sections of this Privacy Policy. 

How We Use Your Child’s Information:

We use the personal information we collect from your child to: 

  * Enable the child to share his or her information and communicate with other users on [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com/schools](https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools), or our mobile applications Buncee Bits, Buncee for Edu, Buncee Pro, and Buncee - A Creative Presentation Tool,;
  * Administer the child’s account with us and customize the service we provide to him or her and other users; and
  * Send the child service or promotional communications through email and notices on the [buncee.com](https://www.buncee.com/), [edu.buncee.com](https://www.edu.buncee.com/), or [edu.buncee.com/schools](https://www.edu.buncee.com/schools) websites. Please Note: For Children under the age of 13, as well as children with accounts under a bunceeEDU PLUS subscription or a bunceeEDU Schools subscription, student sub-accounts will not receive promotional communications from Buncee or our agents.

We use the information we collect automatically through technology (see the “Automatic Information Collection and Tracking” section of this Privacy Policy) and other non-personal information we collect to improve Buncee and to deliver a better and more personalized experience by enabling us to estimate our audience size and usage patterns; store information about the child’s preferences, allowing us to customize the content according to individual interests; and speed up searches on Buncee. 

Our Practices for Disclosing Children’s Information:

We do not share, sell, rent or transfer children’s personal information other than as described in this section. We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual or device. In addition, we may disclose children’s personal information: 

  * To third parties we use to support the internal operations of Buncee and who are bound by contractual or other obligations to use the information only for such purpose and to keep the information confidential.
  * If we are required to do so by law or legal process, such as to comply with any court order or subpoena or to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of Buncee LLC, our customers or others, including to protect the safety of a child; protect the safety and security of Buncee; or enable us to take precautions against liability.
  * To law enforcement agencies or for an investigation related to public safety.

We enable registered users to communicate with others on or through Buncee via email, social media, posting to public areas of Buncee, and links to Third-Party Sites, Products and Services (“Social Features”). The nature of these Social Features allows children to disclose personal information about themselves. Children will not be able to use Social Features until we have obtained verifiable consent as described above under the “Information We Collect From Children” section of this Privacy Policy. We do not monitor, review or control the types of information your child can send or post via Social Features, and we do not control the actions of third parties with whom your child shares his or her information. We encourage parents to educate their children about safe internet use and to carefully monitor their children’s use of Social Features. Please Note: With respect to Student Sub-accounts, students may communicate with others on or through Buncee only via email or by sharing a link or embed code but cannot otherwise upload their digital canvas to social media directly through the Buncee platform. Student accounts maintained within a bunceeEDU Schools account are private by default and are able to email or share a link or embed code but cannot otherwise upload their digital canvas to social media directly through the Buncee platform. The district or school administrator can enable social sharing options for the district, school(s), user type(s), and/or user(s) at their discretion. Buncee may contain links to or allow children to interact with and make use of Third-Party Sites, Products and Services. Access to Third-Party Sites, Products and Services is provided solely as a convenience to our users. Such Third-Party Sites, Products and Services are not under Buncee LLC’s control and Buncee LLC does not necessarily endorse the content, advertising, products, services or other materials on or available from such Third-Party Sites, Products and Services. A child’s use of any Third-Party Sites, Products and Services may be subject to the third-party provider’s terms and conditions and privacy policy and may involve the disclosure or transfer of information from or about the child to the third-party provider. You will need to make your own independent judgment regarding your child’s use of and interaction with any Third-Party Sites, Products and Services. You acknowledge and agree that Buncee LLC is not responsible for the availability of any Third-Party Sites, Products and Services and that Buncee LLC shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with your child’s use of or interaction with any Third-Party Sites, Products and Services. In addition, if Buncee LLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger, consolidation, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, users’ personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. Users will be notified via a prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of personal information. We also provide users with the means to control whether or not his or her profile is viewable to other Buncee users. Student Sub-accounts created by a bunceeEDU PLUS subscriber or a bunceeEDU Schools subscriber are private by default and will only be visible to the subscriber, not to other users. Please Note: With respect to Student Sub-accounts, we do not use or share personal information from children for commercial purposes not related to the provision of the services requested by the educator. 

Accessing and Correcting Your Child’s Personal Information:

At any time, parents and educators may review the child’s personal information maintained by us, require us to correct or delete the personal information and/or refuse to permit us from further collecting or using the child’s information. Parents and educators can review, change or delete their child’s personal information by: 

  * Logging into their child’s account and visiting his or her account profile page.
  * Sending us an email at [privacy@buncee.com](mailto:privacy@buncee.com). To protect your privacy and security, we may require you to take certain steps or provide additional information to verify your identity before we provide any information or make corrections.

Third Party Operators:

We do not have actual knowledge that any third party operators are actively collecting personal information from children through Buncee, and for children under 13 years of age, no third party service providers have access to children’s data. However, as described above, certain content and services offered to children through or in connection with Buncee may be served on websites hosted and operated by Third-Party Sites, Products and Services that are not controlled by or affiliated with Buncee LLC. Buncee LLC does not disclose personal information from children to any Third-Party Sites, Products and Services without the consent of parents, but parents/administrators/educators should be aware that any information children disclose once they access these other websites is not subject to this Privacy Policy. Parents/administrators/educators should review the privacy policy posted on any other website to understand how that third party collects and uses personally identifiable information. The sites on which personal information may be disclosed through Buncee include: 

  * [Facebook, Inc.](https://www.facebook.com/) You can review Facebook’s privacy policy [here](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation).
  * [Twitter, Inc.](https://twitter.com/) You can review Twitter’s privacy policy [here](https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en).
  * [Google Classroom](https://classroom.google.com/). You can review Google Classroom’s privacy policy [here](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).
  * [Google Inc.](https://www.google.com/) You can review Google’s privacy policy [here](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).
  * [Pinterest, Inc.](https://www.pinterest.com/) You can review Pinterest’s privacy policy [here](https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy).
  * [LinkedIn Corporation](https://www.linkedin.com/). You can review LinkedIn’s privacy policy [here](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy).

The sites from which Buncee users may take multimedia (such as photos, videos, audio, text and drawings) when creating their digital canvas on Buncee include: 

  * [YouTube, LLC.](https://www.youtube.com/) You can review YouTube’s privacy policy [here](http://www.youtube.com/t/privacy).
  * [Pixabay](https://pixabay.com/). You can review Pixabay’s privacy policy [here](https://pixabay.com/en/service/privacy/).
  * [Vimeo, LLC.](https://vimeo.com/) You can review Vimeo’s privacy policy [here](https://vimeo.com/privacy).
  * [Flickr. You can review Flickr’s privacy policy ](https://www.flickr.com/)[here](https://policies.yahoo.com/us/en/yahoo/privacy/products/flickr/).

The site(s) which Buncee has selected as a data integration partner include: 

  * [Google Classroom](https://classroom.google.com/). You can review Google Classroom’s privacy policy [here](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).
  * [Clever](https://clever.com/). You can review Clever’s privacy policy [here](https://clever.com/about/privacy-policy).

You may direct your inquiries about any operator’s privacy practices and use of children’s information directly to such operator or to Buncee at: 

Buncee LLC SBU Calverton Business Incubator 4603 Middle Country Road Calverton, NY 11933 Attention: Claire Cucchi Telephone: 631-591-1390 Email: [privacy@buncee.com](mailto:privacy@buncee.com)

Changes to this Section:

If we decide to change this section of our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it periodically. You agree to accept notice of the change by posting here on Buncee, and by your use of Buncee. If we make any changes to this section of our Privacy Policy that materially affect our practices with regard to the personal information we have previously collected from children, we will provide parents/educators with notice and obtain verifiable consent in advance of such change. However, we urge parents/guardians and teachers to instruct their children/students to never give out their real names, addresses, phone numbers, or any other information that would allow someone to identify or contact the child. If you believe that your child has gained access to Buncee without your consent, or if you have any questions or concerns, please contact us at [privacy@buncee.com](mailto:privacy@buncee.com). 

Changes In This Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it. You agree to accept notice of the change by posting here on Buncee, and by your use of Buncee. 

Contact Us:

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, copyright or trademark ownership issues with the content on the site, please contact us at: [privacy@buncee.com](mailto:privacy@buncee.com) or at our office: **Buncee LLC, SBU Calverton Business Incubator, 4603 Middle Country Road, Calverton, NY 11933.**
